(Sheldon:)I went for a walk yesterday
without sunscreen.
(Sheldon:)Do you see anything on my forehead
(Sheldon:)that I should be concerned about?
(Emily:)Um, you know what? I better go.
My movie's about to start.
(Raj:)-Are you here alone?
-No, not really.
-What do you mean, "not really"?
-Hey, should we get our seats?
(Emily:)Yeah. It was nice seeing you.
I'll call you later.
(Raj:)Yeah, okay.
That was awkward, right'?
(Sheldon:)Is it because she's dating you
but was out with that other fellow?
(Sheldon:)-Yes.
-Good.
(Sheldon:)I thought she saw
something on my forehead.
(Director:)And... action.
(Wil Wheaton:)-Please don't shut me out.
Go away.
(Penny:)Just go away.
(Wil:)I swear, I will find
a way to turn you back.
(Penny:)What gave you the right to mix my DNA
with that of a killer gorilla?